[
    {"question": "book", "answer": "books","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "dog", "answer": "dogs","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "cat", "answer": "cats","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "apple", "answer": "apples","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "car", "answer": "cars","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "fish", "answer": "fishes","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "flower", "answer": "flowers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "table", "answer": "tables","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "chair", "answer": "chairs","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "house", "answer": "houses","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "child", "answer": "children","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "friend", "answer": "friends","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "letter", "answer": "letters","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "computer", "answer": "computers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "pen", "answer": "pens","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "window", "answer": "windows","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "door", "answer": "doors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "shoe", "answer": "shoes","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "tree", "answer": "trees","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "road", "answer": "roads","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "city", "answer": "cities","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "country", "answer": "countries","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "bottle", "answer": "bottles","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "glass", "answer": "glasses","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "cup", "answer": "cups","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "plate", "answer": "plates","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "spoon", "answer": "spoons","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "fork", "answer": "forks","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "knife", "answer": "knives","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "food", "answer": "foods","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "drink", "answer": "drinks","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "fruit", "answer": "fruits","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "vegetable", "answer": "vegetables","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "meat", "answer": "meats","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "bird", "answer": "birds","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "animal", "answer": "animals","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "person", "answer": "people","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "boy", "answer": "boys","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "girl", "answer": "girls","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "man", "answer": "men","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "woman", "answer": "women","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "teacher", "answer": "teachers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "student", "answer": "students","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "school", "answer": "schools","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "university", "answer": "universities","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "bookstore", "answer": "bookstores","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "store", "answer": "stores","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "market", "answer": "markets","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "hospital", "answer": "hospitals","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "doctor", "answer": "doctors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "nurse", "answer": "nurses","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "police", "answer": "police officers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "firefighter", "answer": "firefighters","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "soldier", "answer": "soldiers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "pilot", "answer": "pilots","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "engineer", "answer": "engineers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "architect", "answer": "architects","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "lawyer", "answer": "lawyers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "judge", "answer": "judges","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "author", "answer": "authors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "journalist", "answer": "journalists","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "photographer", "answer": "photographers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "artist", "answer": "artists","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "musician", "answer": "musicians","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "singer", "answer": "singers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "actor", "answer": "actors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "director", "answer": "directors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "producer", "answer": "producers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "salesperson", "answer": "salespeople","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "boss", "answer": "bosses","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "secretary", "answer": "secretaries","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "assistant", "answer": "assistants","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "technician", "answer": "technicians","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "mechanic", "answer": "mechanics","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "electrician", "answer": "electricians","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "carpenter", "answer": "carpenters","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "painter", "answer": "painters","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "plumber", "answer": "plumbers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "builder", "answer": "builders","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "farmer", "answer": "farmers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "fisherman", "answer": "fishermen","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "hunter", "answer": "hunters","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "gardener", "answer": "gardeners","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "cook", "answer": "cooks","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "waiter", "answer": "waiters","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "bartender", "answer": "bartenders","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "receptionist", "answer": "receptionists","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "cleaner", "answer": "cleaners","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "driver", "answer": "drivers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "taxi driver", "answer": "taxi drivers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "bus driver", "answer": "bus drivers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "truck driver", "answer": "truck drivers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "train driver", "answer": "train drivers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "flight attendant", "answer": "flight attendants","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "sailor", "answer": "sailors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "captain", "answer": "captains","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "sailor", "answer": "sailors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "scientist", "answer": "scientists","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "scientist", "answer": "scientists","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "teacher", "answer": "teachers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "professor", "answer": "professors","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "student", "answer": "students","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "student", "answer": "students","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "child", "answer": "children","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "youth", "answer": "youths","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "adult", "answer": "adults","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "old person", "answer": "old people","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "friend", "answer": "friends","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "enemy", "answer": "enemies","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "colleague", "answer": "colleagues","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "boss", "answer": "bosses","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "employee", "answer": "employees","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "employer", "answer": "employers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "customer", "answer": "customers","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "patient", "answer": "patients","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "client", "answer": "clients","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "member", "answer": "members","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "English"}
]